dlvrit.com 2019-12-31

# dlvr.it - Privacy Policy

_Effective May 23, 2018_

At dlvr.it, Inc. (“dlvr.it” or “We”) we respect your data security and privacy and are committed to protecting you through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the dlvr.it website at [https://dlvrit.com](https://dlvrit.com/) including all related webpages (the “Site”) or use the dlvr.it service (the “Service”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

Registration with, use of, and access to the Service is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service located at <https://dlvrit.com/terms-of-service>.  Any terms not defined in this Privacy Policy will have the meanings set forth in the dlvr.it Terms of Service.

 **What Information We May Collect**

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual. We obtain Personal Information relating to you from various sources described below.

If you do not provide Personal Information when requested by dlvr.it, you may not be able to utilize the Service if that information is necessary for us to to provide you with the service or if we are legally required to collect it.

We collect Personal Information from you when you register on our site, connect your social media accounts to dlvr.it, communicate with dlvr.it. customer support, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, connect your website or blog to the Service, or otherwise when you directly provide it to us. We also collect information automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.

 **How We May Use The Information We Collect**

We may use the Personal Information we obtain about you to:

  * create and manage your account, provide our Service and respond to your communications;
  * manage account authentication;
  * communicate with you to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance, including by periodically emailing you service-related announcements;
  * tailor our Service (e.g., we may use cookies and similar technologies to remember your preferences);
  * post your content and messages on social media platforms;
  * provide tailored advertising, for dlvr.it services, via Google AdWords or other similar services;
  * aggregate your Personal Information for analytical purposes;
  * provide customer support;
  * operate, analyze and improve our business;
  * send you marketing communications about dlvr.it products, services, offers, programs and promotions;
  * keep the Service safe and secure;
  * manage our customer, service provider and partner relationships;
  * enforce our agreements related to our Service and our other legal rights;
  * comply with applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies;
  * process transactions;
  * administer contests, promotions, surveys or other site features; and
  * provide you with notices about your account and subscription, including expiration and renewal notices.

We may also use the Personal Information we obtain in any other way we may describe when you provide the information and for any other purpose with your consent.

If you are located in the European Economic Area, we may process your Personal Information for the above purposes when:

  * you have consented to the use of your Personal Information, For example, we may seek to obtain your consent for our uses of cookies or similar technologies, or to send you marketing communications.
  * we need your Personal Information to provide you with services and products requested by you, or to respond to your inquiries,
  * we have a legal obligation to use your Personal Information, or
  * we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information. In particular, we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information to ensure and improve the safety, security, and performance of our Service, to anonymize Personal Information and carry out data analyses.

 **How We May Share Your Information**

We may share the Personal Information we collect about you as described below or otherwise disclosed to you at the time the information is collected, including with:

 ** _Social Media Platforms_**

Our main purpose for collecting Personal Information is to allow you to post content on social platforms and enable you to track metrics for analytical purposes. We may allow you to link your dlvr.it account with an account on a third party social network platform, such as Facebook, LinkedIn or Twitter, and to transfer your information to and from the applicable third party platform. Once you share your content to a social media platform, its use will be governed by that platform’s privacy policy.

 _ **Service Providers**_

We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including hosting and maintenance, error monitoring, debugging, performance monitoring, billing, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We may share your Personal Information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services. We also require these third parties to maintain the privacy and security of the Personal Information they process on our behalf.

 _ **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**_

dlvr.it cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. To the extent permitted under applicable law, we may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we believe is necessary or appropriate to investigate, respond to, and defend against claims, for legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of dlvr.it or a third party, to protect dlvr.it against liability, for the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, fraudulent, abusive, or legally actionable activity, to protect the security or integrity of the Service and any equipment used to make the Service available, or to comply with the law.

 _ **Business Transfers**_

We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets, or similar transaction, or in the event of insolvency or bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity’s planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

 _ **Other Third Parties**_

We may share Personal Information with affiliates and business partners to whom it is reasonably necessary or desirable for us to disclose your data for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We may also make certain non-Personal Information available to third parties for various purposes, including for business or marketing purposes or to assist third parties in understanding our users’ interest, habits, and usage patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and functionality available through the Service.

 **How We Protect Your Information**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your Personal Information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your Personal Information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

Due to the nature of the Internet and online communications, however, we cannot guarantee that any information transmitted online will remain confidential. We are not liable for the illegal acts of third parties such as criminal hackers.

 **Do Not Track Requests**

We do not process or respond to web browsers’ “do not track” signals or other similar transmissions that indicate a request to disable online tracking of users who use our Service.

 **Cookies and Related Technologies**

Like many websites, we also use “cookie” technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our Service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our Service.

We may also automatically record certain information from your device by using various types of technology, including “clear gifs” or “web beacons.” This automatically collected information may include your IP address or other device address or ID, web browser and/or device type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after you use the Service, the pages or other content you view or otherwise interact with on the Service, and the dates and times that you visit, access, or use the Service. We also may use these technologies to collect information regarding your interaction with email messages, such as whether you opened, clicked on, or forwarded a message, to the extent permitted under applicable law.

You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. Please note that if you delete, or choose not to accept, cookies from the Service, you may not be able to utilize the features of the Service to their fullest potential.

 **Children’s Privacy**

The Service is not directed to persons under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [privacy@dlvr.it](mailto:privacy@dlvr.it). We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 18. If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

 **Your Rights**

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such marketing communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. Please be aware that, even after you opt out from receiving marketing messages from us, you will continue to receive administrative messages from dlvr.it regarding the Service.

In certain jurisdictions you have the right to request access and receive information about the Personal Information we maintain about you, to update and correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information, to restrict or object to the processing of your Personal Information, to have the information blocked, anonymized or deleted, as appropriate, or to exercise your right to data portability to transfer your Personal Information to another company. Those rights may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements. In addition to the above-mentioned rights, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with a competent supervisory authority subject to applicable law.

Where required by law, we obtain your consent for the processing of certain Personal Information collected by cookies or similar technologies, or used to send you direct marketing communications, or when we carry out other processing activities for which consent may be required. If we rely on consent for the processing of your Personal Information, you have the right to withdraw it at any time and free of charge. When you do so, this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent withdrawal.

To update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists, delete your account or submit a request to exercise your rights under applicable law, please contact us as specified in the “Contact Us” section below.

 **California Privacy Rights**

Residents of California have the right to request a disclosure describing what types of personal information we have shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes, and with whom we have shared it, during the preceding year. You may request a copy of that disclosure by contacting us at [privacy@dlvr.it](mailto:privacy@dlvr.it).

 **Links to Other Websites**

Our Site and Service contain may contain links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Personal Information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personal Information you submit to them. We are not responsible for the content, privacy and security practices, and policies of third-party sites or services to which links or access are provided through the Service. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

 **Data Transfers**

dlvr.it is based in the United States. Personal Information that we collect may be transferred to, and stored at, any of our affiliates, partners or service providers which may be inside or outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and Switzerland, including the United States. By submitting your personal data, you agree to such transfers. Your Personal Information may be transferred to countries that do not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer or disclose your Personal Information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

 **Updates To Our Privacy Policy**

Our Privacy Policy may be updated at any time for any reason. We will notify you of any updates to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site and indicating the date of the latest revision. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any modifications.

Your continued use of the Service after any updates to the Privacy Policy indicates that you have read, understood and agreed to the current version of this Privacy Policy.

 **International Use**

The Service is intended for visitors located within the United States. We make no representation that the Service is appropriate or available for use outside of the United States. Access to the Service from countries or territories or by individuals where such access is illegal is prohibited

 **Contact Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

dlvr.it, Inc.  
6663 SW Beaverton Hillsdale Hwy #71  
Portland, OR 97225
